My...
my strength, it's... it's gone. I...
I can't lift...
Miseria.
Even my vision's blurry. Dammit.
Is this it?
I knew this moment would come.
But why now?
I must press on.
Huh? What did...
Wait, that's right.
Bucciarati and his crew are
trying to get somewhere right now.
This could be my chance to learn where.
I know the boss is desperate to find out.
Um, uh, looks like you could use a hand.
Here, I'm happy to
assist you if you'd like.
You again?
Why are you still here?
I'll be fine.
You should get to safety.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to seem pushy or anything.
I just want to make sure
you get across safely.
It would put me at ease
if you let me help.
I mean, um, only if you don't mind.
On second thought, I suppose
I could use a touch of help.
Where are we heading, good sir?
Not too far.
Just the entrance to the Coliseum.
So that's where you're trying to get to.
Thank you
so
much for watching.
Don't care, don't care
You hear it, don't you?
When your body dies,
I'll be here to help you?
Hell, no!
It's the beginning of the doorbell ring
Watch out!
Hey, are you okay?
You gotta look both ways
when you're cr - Huh?
What the?
His hands are so cold and clammy.
I'm sorry.
This thing I just tripped on.
Is it a guardrail?
Hold on a second.
Does this mean he can't see anymore?
And he didn't even flinch when
that driver honked his horn.
Are his ears busted too?
That gas you have on your throat.
Did I...
Did I do that to you
in the scuffle earlier?
No, that's probably not the case.
The wound has already stopped bleeding.
That means it's older.
How'd you manage to hurt yourself there?
He's staring right at it.
So he can't still see?
Wait, but it's hidden under my collar.
Or the injury I got from fighting Risotto.
How kind of you to help me pick that
up. Crazy mille. I'll take that.
Now then, let's get going.
Well, all right.
So he can hear me.
Still, whatever's ailing him seems way
more complex than just battle wounds.
What's making him act like this?
Oh, shit.
It's Guido Mista. Figures.
I knew things were going too well.
Should have guessed his friends
wouldn't be too far behind.
Is something the matter?
What's wrong?
We've yet to finish crossing.
I'm sorry. It's just...
I need to sit down.
My wound opened up.
I'll just be a minute, I swear.
Crap, crap, crap!
He's coming!
Excuse my bluntness,
but I need to get going.
Thank you for all the help
you've given me so far.
No, not now!
I need you to stay here!
I mean, there's another car coming.
We can keep crossing once it passes.
It's fine.
We've already cleared
that side of the road.
It should be safe to continue.
Come on, the clock's ticking.
Damn it! No! Mista's coming!
I'll just have to kill
him! Right here! Right now!
Oh my goodness, I wonder what
that noise could have been.
For God's sake, what now?
What perplexing game are you playing?
Why do you have to call now of all times?
Do you want him to find out?
Wait a second.
Would you quit blowing me up, dude?
What's so damn important, you
gotta tell me right this second.
You're gonna blow my freaking cover.
Trish, get back inside the turtle.
We're not out of the woods yet.
Please keep a low head for now.
No, wait.
We're not alone.
I can sense him.
He's here, I'm sure of it.
That horrible feeling.
There's no mistaking it.
It's the same one.
Wait.
I know you.
I finally recognize you.
You're…
Trish!
I feel it. He's nearby.
The boss is closing in on us.
Tell me which way to shoot.
Can you tell us exactly where he is?
He suddenly appeared, but
I can't pinpoint where.
You're safe.
Thank the heavens above.
Excellent work.
You've achieved an incredible feat,
although I expect nothing
short of perfection from you.
Rest assured.
Bujarati's eyes may
seem to be fixed on you?
but he does not truly see you.
Wait, what?
I don't get it.
I possess no insight as to how,
but he's now a reanimated corpse.
He lacks both a pulse and a
working respiratory system.
He's lost use of his eyes, and his eardrums
were ruptured in his fight with Seko.
The only thing he's able to see,
Deep, is a rough outline of your soul.
The only sound he can
hear are its vibrations.
Physical objects are now invisible to him.
He sees not the car, but the
essence of the driver within.
Trish, talk to me.
Did something happen to you?
It just so happens my daughter
and I am at near-identical auras.
And for the moment, I
have cloaked you in mine.
Bucciarati presently believes
he is looking at Trish.
You must maintain this illusion.
Let him be your personal guide and have
him take you to this secret meeting.
Trish.
I'm so sorry.
I think I got a little lightheaded.
But thank goodness.
I'm relieved to see you're okay.
Yeah, I am.
By the way, have you seen
a young man anywhere?
Oh yeah, I think so.
He looked kind of flustered
and left in a big hurry.
We shouldn't worry about him, though.
Right now, we need to
stay focused on moving.
You're right.
I'm sorry, but could...
Could you give me a little hand, please?
Yes.
I'd be glad to.
In the outskirts of Napoli.
I...
I have a house.
It isn't big, but when this is all over,
by chance you find yourself needing a home,
you'll be more than welcome there.
You know, the area's pretty nice.
Good eats and everything.
And it's close to the beach.
I know this has all
been one big nightmare,
but I promise a much
brighter future is waiting.
Sounds nice, but let's stay focused.
Which way do you want me to steer us next?
The stairs, please, if you don't mind.
You mean these?
Do not turn around, Dobio!
Just keep going!
Continue onward as if nothing happened.
Someone's here.
Behind the stone pillars above,
someone is watching your every move.
So, he really is here to
rendezvous with our foes.
But who could they be?
I've zero intel on this person.
How are you so sure that
they're really here, boss?
I mean, even if you're right,
how am I supposed to figure out who
they are if I can't turn around?
Look into Butorati's eyes.
They will tell you.
Quick, while the reflection's there!
Don't move.
Stay right where you are.
Get a step closer to those stairs,
and our agreement will be nullified.
You were right. Crap.
Someone's hiding out behind the pillar.
I saw him.
My name is Bruno Bucciarati.
I've come here on your promise
to reveal the boss's weakness.
I hope you mean to keep your word.
You, I know.
The problem's your friend.
I never said you could bring a plus one.
I can't find a shred of
data on them in my records.
Of course you wouldn't.
Trish here isn't a member of the Family.
In fact, we met barely
more than a few days ago.
But as you can clearly
see, she's batting for us.
Trish, you say?
To my knowledge, that's a woman's name.
Your point?
Merida, I think the jig's
up, boss. Calm down.
Listen, you must respond.
Act furious at him for
doubting your femininity.
Do it, Deep.
You got some kind of problem
with me being a girl, you pig?
My deepest apologies, mademoiselle.
I can't see very well in this light.
Is the lady a stand user?
Yes, she is.
Now down to business.
I think it's about time
you tell us who you are.
Let's talk about why you dragged me here.
No, not yet.
I'd like to see her stand first.
And Trish.
No sudden movements.
I have no data on you.
But show me your stand and I'll get
over it. Shit! What now? Damn it.
It appears we're dealing
with a seasoned gladiator.
He's even trying to gauge
a potential enemy's range.
Who is this man?
How have I never heard of him?
What's wrong now?
Shouldn't be too hard.
Think of it like lifting up
your skirt nice and slow.
That's... But how?
How does he possess that?
That arrow...
There's no doubt.
It's the same artifact.
And that bloodlust, it's overwhelming.
It almost feels like a
dagger racing for my heart.
Where have I felt this before?
Mon Dieu!
Wait, that's right.
I have crossed paths with this man.
He utilized the arrow to
track me down back then.
I remember!
In Egypt, I unearthed a scattering of
arrows was capable of awakening stands.
I knew simply from beholding them, they
possessed a certain entrancing energy.
An old woman by the name of
Nyaba, who had two right hands,
asked that I sell her some in
exchange for their secrets.
In truth, I only needed one, so I sold her
the other five for a very generous sum.
That is when the old bag uttered
something I found truly bizarre.
The arrow chooses people, and those
chosen are bound by a curious force.
The 20th century was in its final
decade, and Dio had passed. At the time,
my old friend Jotaro Kujo and I were
investigating the arrow
which could awaken Stans.
Word had reached us of a young
boy who had pilfered them
so he split up and scoured
the globe for the bastard.
Jotaro would search America and Asia,
And I, Europe and Africa, I soon managed
to learn the arrow was somewhere in Italy,
hidden in a region suddenly
overcome by drug-related crimes.
I focused my search on
a specific region where
juvenile drug deaths had
seen an unusual jump.
That's when I knew we were getting close.
However...
In a few years, my syndicate
was on the cusp of perfection.
My Family swore allegiance to me.
I had men in every crevice of society.
Then I discovered that someone was
plotting to unveil my identity.
In the end, I'd finish them off myself.
It was the only way.
I'd made my decision.
Ultimately I committed two fatal errors.
First was my failure to recognize this
syndicate had already
matured to full strength.
Communications, the government, the
press, society had me completely isolated.
Then came my second and grievous mistake.
Silver chariot.
Since you're about to die,
I might as well tell you
the man who would unearth
those arrows he possessed
a power many times more.
than I could ever imagine!
Long before your gaze
can hope to reach me!
His ability breaks time!
You'll have already left this world!
Has hope...
Perished from the Earth, too?
I was certain I'd finish the job,
to think one of them
would return from death,
and with the arrow in
their grasp, no less.
Butcherati, that man's no friend of ours.
What?
Butcherati, that bastard,
where'd he run off to?
He's gone.
Putan, where did he go, that little
uninvited guest of yours, where is he?
Datrice...
Answer me, dammit, where the hell
is that swine you brought with you?
Nothing seemed to fall, but somehow
the broken piece found its way here.
It couldn't be these movements.
Did you see?
Time to skip forward.
Just like what happened in Venice.
We climbed the stairs
before we realized it.
We won't make it.
He's already there. The boss.
He's got our guy within his range!
I'm being tested.
In a moment, we will find out if
I'm prepared to vanquish my past.
We really only grow once we've conquered
our phantoms, wouldn't you say?
How lovely to see you again,
Jean-Pierre Polnareff.
I know you!
Diavolo!
Fascinating how the past
can wriggle its way back,
no matter how many pieces
I might cut it up into.
You amaze me, I never thought I'd deal
with the same vermin more than once.
How did you slither up here?
Let me be perfectly clear.
I couldn't care less
about how you managed to
live after I slung you
like chum into the abyss.
What interests me, Polnareff,
is whatever little secret you were all so
eager to share with
Butcherati and his men!
Walk up those steps and
see what happens, asshole!
I have the high ground while
you're stuck way down there!
Why do you shrink from battling me?
Do I scare you?
Has your spirit lost some of its vigor?
Or has your body now given in to time?
What are you plotting with the arrow?
This is impossible!
I'm sure it was a kid I saw down there!
Malodorous wretch!
When did you get so close to me?!
The high ground is mine! En Card!
Say your goodbyes to that arrow!
Once I've sent you back to the depths of
hell, you'll have no further need for it!
There!
Silver Terunosu!
Still sharp as ever, I see.
You in that stand of yours.
Seems you've learned a new trick, too.
You're trying to pinpoint
the moments I skip
through time by keeping
count of the blood drops.
Resourceful.
A moment's difference reveals so much.
Your grasp of time is masterful.
Had I gone just a little bit closer, you
might have dealt a consequential blow.
Unbelievable!
How did Diablo reach the
Colosseum before the others?
This is it.
It's now or never.
Whatever it takes, I have to
keep the flames of hope alive.
You died the second you were in range.
I'll I'll make sure you stay
that way, Emperor Crimson!
When the sands of time resume,
you'll no longer be able to look?
at your precious blood drops for guidance.
A cursed mistake from my past.
Behold, I shall obliterate you now! Die!
Enjoy the fatal relief that time will...
What's happening?
The arrow! The stand!
This nonsense will cease! Perish!
This radiance!
What's happening to Silver Chariot?
Such sheer power!
The arrow's bursting with it!
This ends now!
Time resume your flow!
French rat, what now?
No, don't tell me, is the arrow able to do
more than draw out the power of a stand?
It's a long shot, but there's no other
way of keeping the arrow from him.
It pains me that I had to show him.
However, I can no longer deny I've lost
the strength to fully control the arrow.
You can't run!
The arrow is hope-given form.
Whosoever comes to control it will
be able to control the world as well.
Huh?
It just happened again.
Did you feel it?
There was a blip in time.
Trish, where'd you sense the boss?
All those wasted years trying to
uncover the mystery of the arrow.
I'm surprised you made it this long.
What an utter travesty!
The arrow is mine, you fool!
Your valiant heart has
stopped beating at last.
If it offers you any solace, know
that you did not die in vain.
Fine, dear Jean-Bierre Polnareff.
You've done me a greater service
than you'll ever realize.
I tell you that sincerely.
Giorno!
I found Bucciarati! He's
right there! Come on! Shit!
Poor guy got pummeled hard!
Bucciarati! Be careful!
The boss is lurking somewhere near!
You've come.
What?
Stop now! Who are you?
Identify yourself immediately!
What is just fiction or what is the truth?
They have a mission, they have a passion.
But they dare to tell us
what's bad and what's good!
Stand up, join us.
Come on, I'll say this a lie.
We are the power, who'll be the future!
Cause we are the fighters,
just fighting for
Thank
you.